What's wrong?
Bite your tongue?
No.
My tooth is kind of
wobbly.
Don't touch it!
What should I do?
Your adult tooth is growing in, so just leave it.
Do you want to eat porridge instead?
No, it'll be fine if I chew slowly.
School
Festival
Daikichi!
Hey.
What is it?
That's the one I drew!
Kaga
Rin
Rin-chan, it's always your dad who comes here, isn't it?
He's not my dad, though.
He's not?
That's pretty good.
You know, Rin-chan is the best at drawing in Class B.
You could become a manga artist.
No way.
You could!
Papa!
Over here!
Sorry for the wait.
This good-looking guy is a dad?
He's so cool!
Isn't he great?
He's so tall!
You know, Sayaka-san's dad is 31, just like you.
Seriously?
Is that so? What a happy coincidence.
My papa is a model!
Wow!
Hey now, Sayaka!
Just a little when I was younger.
I think I might've seen you in our company's catalog.
Really?
Could you tell me the name of that company?
Then it's probably me!
I'm very grateful towards them.
What a carefree guy.
I'm a manager for the same agency now.
Oh, I see.
Seems like a waste.
Both the working hours and pay were pretty unpredictable,
so I quit after my daughter was born.
Around that time, I'd be drinking and complaining about work all the time.
Hey, Miki-chan!
Nabe-chin! It's been a while!
He's a classmate.
We grew up around here.
He has a son in Class A.
This is Rin-chan's dad, Daikichi-san.
He's the same age as us.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
These people are already at the parenting stage.
Daikichi!
I'm a butcher.
On the corner of the shopping district.
Rin and I buy croquettes there all the time.
Really? Happy to hear that!
Me too!
Yeah, I know!
I just became friends with some dads.
In a way, the world seems a bit bigger here.
Good afternoon.
It's gotten cold all of a sudden.
Yes.
Looks like the kids have already gone to P.E.
I hope they're wearing their jackets.
Yeah.
Nitani
Kouki
That's really good!
Really?
Looks like he put a lot of effort into-
You know,
all the other kids are at P.E already.
Seriously?
This is bad!
The teacher's going to yell at me!
Boys sure can be a handful.
So cute!
How old?
Almost 10 months.
Babies are so nice.
This brings back memories.
You know, my kid got the flu last week.
Sorry to make you wait!
I see.
Must be troublesome.
It's that season already, huh?
They need to stay home for two days even after the fever subsides.
They're still contagious.
I sent my kid to school right after the fever went away.
I guess it's unavoidable. You'd get fired from work.
Well, it was pretty much gone anyway, so the virus would be weak too, right?
Yeah.
Even if someone did catch the flu, no one would know who it was from.
Let's get out of here.
Um, I...
I kind of understand where those people were coming from.
So I'm just a bit depressed.
The talk about their jobs and such. I sort of understand.
Yeah, you're right.
When it starts to get cold, I get so nervous.
But Kouki...
Hurry and get into your pajamas!
But once winter ends, and it starts to get warm again,
I can finally breathe a sigh of relief.
Daikichi!
Daikichi, give me a minute to get my schoolbag.
What's wrong with you guys?!
Kouki, your nose!
Didn't I tell you to put your jackets on?!
And don't run in the hallways!
Okay!
No running, I said!
Kouki is already losing his teeth.
Even though we live in an apartment,
he doesn't listen and throws them onto the roof.
TL Note: Baby teeth are thrown onto the roof as a charm to make the new teeth grow properly.
Lately, he hasn't been listening to a word I say.
I don't have the right to talk about others.
Wearing as little clothing as possible.
Running down the stairs two at a time.
Eating really fast and gulping down the milk.
It feels really weird to warn kids not to do the things I did as a kid.
Daikichi-san, you used to do all that?
I think it's pretty normal for a boy.
Besides, I can't think of Kouki as a stranger.
I'm sorry!
But if you were like that too,
I'm a bit relieved.
What's wrong? Why don't you walk with Kouki?
I don't want to!
Let's split up the guys and girls.
Isn't Rin-chan's face a little red?
Rin-chan probably has a fever.
It might get worse.
She's a lot more flushed than usual!
It doesn't appear to be the flu.
I'd advise members of the family to wear a mask, just in case.
Right.
Isn't that great?
Are you done already?
Yeah. This part feels weird.
The doctor said it's a stomach infection, so no need to force yourself.
Yeah. I feel...
Rin!
L-Let me get a washbowl!
Rin-chan is what?
Call an ambulance now!
Well, I already had her checked out and got some medicine,
but she refuses to take it.
Her fever keeps increasing, and she looks like she's in pain.
I bet you let her go out wearing light clothes!
Who cares about that now?
Mix the medicine with some juice!
You'd drink it right away if I mixed it with something sweet.
I'll try that.
Thank you, Mom.
Here, try some.
It's sweet.
Here, just a little.
Daikichi.
Sorry to come by so early.
How's Rin-chan?
I'm sorry!
Can I come in?
Daikichi, what's with that hair?
Yes.
It's not the flu, apparently.
Kouki, go watch some TV.
Okay.
Keep the volume down.
She finally fell asleep earlier.
The fever just keeps going up,
and she has trouble sleeping.
She isn't sweating at all, either.
Did you give her any fluids?
I was told to at least give her sports drinks,
but she won't drink or eat.
I don't know what to do.
W-What's wrong?
You can't lose your cool!
An adult has to stay calm and tell them they'll be all right.
That's impossible.
I've never seen Rin like this before.
No, it's not! You can do it!
When they're in trouble, kids really depend on others to help them.
Rin-chan will be fine as long as you're here.
Rin-chan.
Kouki-kun's mom.
You must be thirsty.
Do you want to eat some ice?
How is it?
Feels good.
Rin! You're awake?
Sorry, I had to use the restroom.
Daikichi-san!
I'm sorry.
You can have some more ice after a while.
If you eat too much at once, you'll upset your stomach.
Okay.
I just put something sweet and delicious in the fridge.
I'm sorry. I made you late for work, didn't I?
Rin-chan is trying really hard.
As long as you're there for her, she'll be fine.
Right. Thank you very much.
You too, Kouki.
Right.
Sorry, I might have to take tomorrow off too.
Please give me a call if something comes up.
Sure!
Sorry for the trouble.
What are you saying?
Just leave everything to us!
Thank you.
Want to eat a little more?
Okay.
Once you're better, you can eat all the sweets you want.
Later.
Okay.
Just sleep a little more, and you'll be fine.
Why did it have to be Rin?
If it were me, it wouldn't have been so bad.
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Coming.
Hey, Daikichi!
Kouki!
How are you feeling, Rin-chan? Does it hurt anywhere?
I'm fine.
I'll make you some tasty porridge.
Her fever has been going up again since the afternoon.
It's fine. Fevers tend to go down in the morning and go back up in the afternoon.
But it went above 39 degrees earlier.
Here! Put this in the pot.
O-Okay.
Daikichi...
Water...
Looks delicious.
There's enough for you too.
Daikichi, Rin wants some water!
Got it!
Kouki, stay here so you don't catch anything from her, okay?
Even if I do, it's fine.
Of course it isn't!
Thank you.
Kouki-kun, thank you.
Rin feels a lot more relaxed when you're here, Kouki.
Okay, Rin-chan. Want to eat a little?
It'll be fine.
Kouki eats this when he gets sick.
It's a special porridge that'll make you feel better.
Kouki-kun too?
That's right. When he eats this, he gets better in no time.
It's delicious!
Daikichi!
Rin! Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
I'm hungry.
Tell your mom I really appreciated her help.
She took care of Rin, after all.
Can I go home with you?
That again?
You're supposed to go home with your mom!
Mom's in bed with a cold.
What? Seriously?